0 0 Story of a man who has unnatural feelings for a pig. Starts out with a opening scene that is a terrific example of absurd comedy. A formal orchestra audience is turned into an insane, violent mob by the crazy chantings of it's singers. Unfortunately it stays absurd the WHOLE time with no general narrative eventually making it just too off putting. Even those from the era should be turned off. The cryptic dialogue would make <PERSON>Shakespeare</PERSON> seem easy to a third grader. On a technical level it's better than you might think with some good cinematography by future great <PERSON>Vilmos Zsigmond</PERSON>. Future stars <PERSON>Sally Kirkland</PERSON> and <PERSON>Frederic Forrest</PERSON> can be seen briefly.
1 1 <ORGANIZATION>Bromwell High</ORGANIZATION> is a cartoon comedy. It ran at the same time as some other programs about school life, such as "Teachers". My 35 years in the teaching profession lead me to believe that <PERSON>Bromwell High</PERSON>'s satire is much closer to reality than is "Teachers". The scramble to survive financially, the insightful students who can see right through their pathetic teachers' pomp, the pettiness of the whole situation, all remind me of the schools I knew and their students. When I saw the episode in which a student repeatedly tried to burn down the school, I immediately recalled ......... at .......... High. A classic line: INSPECTOR: I'm here to sack one of your teachers. STUDENT: Welcome to <ORGANIZATION>Bromwell High</ORGANIZATION>. I expect that many adults of my age think that <ORGANIZATION>Bromwell High</ORGANIZATION> is far fetched. What a pity that it isn't!
2 0 <PERSON>Robert DeNiro</PERSON> plays the most unbelievably intelligent illiterate of all time. This movie is so wasteful of talent, it is truly disgusting. The script is unbelievable. The dialog is unbelievable. <PERSON>Jane Fonda</PERSON>'s character is a caricature of herself, and not a funny one. The movie moves at a snail's pace, is photographed in an ill-advised manner, and is insufferably preachy. It also plugs in every cliche in the book. <PERSON>Swoozie Kurtz</PERSON> is excellent in a supporting role, but so what?<br /><br />Equally annoying is this new <ORGANIZATION>IMDB</ORGANIZATION> rule of requiring ten lines for every review. When a movie is this worthless, it doesn't require ten lines of text to let other readers know that it is a waste of time and tape. Avoid this movie.
3 1 If you like adult comedy cartoons, like <LOCATION>South Park</LOCATION>, then this is nearly a similar format about the small adventures of three teenage girls at <ORGANIZATION>Bromwell High</ORGANIZATION>. <PERSON>Keisha</PERSON>, <PERSON>Natella</PERSON> and <PERSON>Latrina</PERSON> have given exploding sweets and behaved like bitches, I think <PERSON>Keisha</PERSON> is a good leader. There are also small stories going on with the teachers of the school. There's the idiotic principal, Mr. <PERSON>Bip</PERSON>, the nervous Maths teacher and many others. The cast is also fantastic, <PERSON>Lenny Henry</PERSON>'s <PERSON>Gina Yashere</PERSON>, EastEnders <PERSON>Chrissie Watts</PERSON>, <PERSON>Tracy-Ann Oberman</PERSON>, Smack The Pony's <PERSON>Doon Mackichan</PERSON>, Dead Ringers' <PERSON>Mark Perry</PERSON> and <PERSON>Blunder</PERSON>'s <PERSON>Nina Conti</PERSON>. I didn't know this came from <LOCATION>Canada</LOCATION>, but it is very good. Very good!
4 0 I saw the capsule comment said "great acting." In my opinion, these are two great actors giving horrible performances, and with zero chemistry with one another, for a great director in his all-time worst effort. <PERSON>Robert De Niro</PERSON> has to be the most ingenious and insightful illiterate of all time. <PERSON>Jane Fonda</PERSON>'s performance uncomfortably drifts all over the map as she clearly has no handle on this character, mostly because the character is so poorly written. Molasses-like would be too swift an adjective for this film's excruciating pacing. Although the film's intent is to be an uplifting story of curing illiteracy, watching it is a true "bummer." I give it 1 out of 10, truly one of the worst 20 movies for its budget level that I have ever seen.
5 1 <ORGANIZATION>Bromwell High</ORGANIZATION> is nothing short of brilliant. Expertly scripted and perfectly delivered, this searing parody of a students and teachers at a <ORGANIZATION>South London Public School</ORGANIZATION> leaves you literally rolling with laughter. It's vulgar, provocative, witty and sharp. The characters are a superbly caricatured cross section of British society (or to be more accurate, of any society). Following the escapades of <PERSON>Keisha</PERSON>, <PERSON>Latrina</PERSON> and <PERSON>Natella</PERSON>, our three "protagonists" for want of a better term, the show doesn't shy away from parodying every imaginable subject. Political correctness flies out the window in every episode. If you enjoy shows that aren't afraid to poke fun of every taboo subject imaginable, then <ORGANIZATION>Bromwell High</ORGANIZATION> will not disappoint!
6 0 If I had not read <PERSON>Pat Barker</PERSON>'s 'Union Street' before seeing this film, I would have liked it. Unfortuntately this is not the case. It is actually my kind of film, it is well made, and in no way do I want to say otherwise, but as an adaptation, it fails from every angle.<br /><br />The harrowing novel about the reality of living in a northern <LOCATION>England</LOCATION> working-class area grabbed hold of my heartstrings and refused to let go for weeks after I had finished. I was put through tears, repulsion, shock, anger, sympathy and misery when reading about the women of <LOCATION>Union Street</LOCATION>. Excellent. A novel that at times I felt I could not read any more of, but I novel I simply couldn't put down. Depressing yes, but utterly gripping.<br /><br />The film. Oh dear. <LOCATION>Hollywood</LOCATION> took <PERSON>Barker</PERSON>'s truth and reality, and showered a layer of sweet icing sugar over the top of it. A beautiful film, an inspiring soundtrack, excellent performances, a tale of hope and romance...yes. An adaptation of 'Union Street'...no.<br /><br />The women of Union Street and their stories are condensed into <PERSON>Fonda</PERSON>'s character, their stories are touched on, but many are discarded. I accept that some of <PERSON>Barker</PERSON>'s tales are sensitive issues and are too horrific for mass viewing, and that a film with around 7 leading protagonists just isn't practical, but the content is not my main issue. The essence and the real gut of the novel is lost - darkness and rain, broken windows covered with cardboard, and the graphically described stench of poverty is replaced with sunshine, pretty houses, and a twinkling <PERSON>William</PERSON>'s score.<br /><br />If you enjoyed the film for its positivity and hope in the face of 'reality', I advise that you hesitate to read the book without first preparing yourself for something more like 'Schindler's List'...but without the happy ending.
7 1 "All the world's a stage and its people actors in it"--or something like that. Who the hell said that theatre stopped at the orchestra pit--or even at the theatre door? Why is not the audience participants in the theatrical experience, including the story itself?<br /><br />This film was a grand experiment that said: "Hey! the story is you and it needs more than your attention, it needs your active participation". "Sometimes we bring the story to you, sometimes you have to go to the story."<br /><br />Alas no one listened, but that does not mean it should not have been said.
8 0 This fanciful horror flick has <PERSON>Vincent Price</PERSON> playing a mad magician that realizes his vocational talents have been sold to another. He devise ways of avenging all those that have wronged him. His master scheme seems to back fire on him.<br /><br />Price is a little below par compared to his masterpieces, but is still the only reason to watch this thriller. Supporting cast includes <PERSON>Patrick O'Neal</PERSON>, <PERSON>Mary Murphy</PERSON>, <PERSON>Eva Gabor</PERSON> and <PERSON>Jay Novello</PERSON>.<br /><br />
9 1 FUTZ is the only show preserved from the experimental theatre movement in <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> in the 1960s (the origins of Off Off <LOCATION>Broadway</LOCATION>). Though it's not for everyone, it is a genuinely brilliant, darkly funny, even more often deeply disturbing tale about love, sex, personal liberty, and revenge, a serious morality tale even more relevant now in a time when <ORGANIZATION>Congress</ORGANIZATION> wants to outlaw gay marriage by trashing our Constitution. The story is not about being gay, though -- it's about love and sex that don't conform to social norms and therefore must be removed through violence and hate. On the surface, it tells the story of a man who falls in love with a pig, but like any great fable, it's not really about animals, it's about something bigger -- stifling conformity in <LOCATION>America</LOCATION>.<br /><br />The stage version won international acclaim in its original production, it toured the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>, and with others of its kind, influenced almost all theatre that came after it. Luckily, we have preserved here the show pretty much as it was originally conceived, with the original cast and original director, <PERSON>Tom O'Horgan</PERSON> (who also directed HAIR and <PERSON>Jesus Christ Superstar</PERSON> on <LOCATION>Broadway</LOCATION>).<br /><br />This is not a mainstream, easy-to-take, studio film -- this is an aggressive, unsettling, glorious, deeply emotional, wildly imaginative piece of storytelling that you'll never forget. And it just might change the way you see the world...
10 0 I basically skimmed through the movie but just enough to catch watch the plot was about. To tell you the truth it was kind of boring to me and at some spots it didn't make sense. The only reason I watched this movie in the first place was to see <PERSON>CHACE CRAWFORD</PERSON>!!! He is so hot, but in this movie his hair was kind of weird. But still hot.<br /><br />However, despite how hot CHACE is, it really did not make up for the film. I guess the plot isn't that bad but what really threw me over was the fact that they cuss in like every sentence. Is it that hard to express your anger without saying the F word every time?The cussing was annoying and the whole flashy, camera shaking thing gave me a headache.<br /><br />All in all, although the plot was OK, I found the film to be a bore and over dramatic. That's why I only cut to scenes with <PERSON>CHACE</PERSON> in it. LOL Anyways, not worth renting unless your a die-hard fan of a specific cast member like I was. Oh yeah the cast was Hot. The girls were HOT!!! But <PERSON>CHACE</PERSON> IS THE BEST!!
11 1 I came in in the middle of this film so I had no idea about any credits or even its title till I looked it up here, where I see that it has received a mixed reception by your commentators. I'm on the positive side regarding this film but one thing really caught my attention as I watched: the beautiful and sensitive score written in a Coplandesque Americana style. My surprise was great when I discovered the score to have been written by none other than <PERSON>John Williams</PERSON> himself. True he has written sensitive and poignant scores such as <ORGANIZATION>Schindler</ORGANIZATION>'s List but one usually associates his name with such bombasticities as Star Wars. But in my opinion what <PERSON>Williams</PERSON> has written for this movie surpasses anything I've ever heard of his for tenderness, sensitivity and beauty, fully in keeping with the tender and lovely plot of the movie. And another recent score of his, for Catch Me if You Can, shows still more wit and sophistication. As to <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> and <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>, I like education movies like How Green was my <LOCATION>Valley</LOCATION> and <PERSON>Konrack</PERSON>, that one with <PERSON>John Voigt</PERSON> and his young African American charges in <LOCATION>South Carolina</LOCATION>, and <PERSON>Danny deVito</PERSON>'s Renaissance Man, etc. They tell a necessary story of intellectual and spiritual awakening, a story which can't be told often enough. This one is an excellent addition to that genre.
12 0 From the beginning of the movie, it gives the feeling the director is trying to portray something, what I mean to say that instead of the story dictating the style in which the movie should be made, he has gone in the opposite way, he had a type of move that he wanted to make, and wrote a story to suite it. And he has failed in it very badly. I guess he was trying to make a stylish movie. Any way I think this movie is a total waste of time and effort. In the credit of the director, he knows the media that he is working with, what I am trying to say is I have seen worst movies than this. Here at least the director knows to maintain the continuity in the movie. And the actors also have given a decent performance.
13 1 Fair drama/love story movie that focuses on the lives of blue collar people finding new life thru new love.The acting here is good but the film fails in cinematography,screenplay,directing and editing.The story/script is only average at best.This film will be enjoyed by <PERSON>Fonda</PERSON> and <PERSON>De Niro</PERSON> fans and by people who love middle age love stories where in the coartship is on a more wiser and cautious level.It would also be interesting for people who are interested on the subject matter regarding illiteracy.......
14 0 This is really a new low in entertainment. Even though there are a lot worse movies out.<br /><br />In the Gangster / Drug scene genre it is hard to have a convincing storyline (this movies does not, i mean Sebastians motives for example couldn't be more far fetched and worn out clichÃ©.) Then you would also need a setting of character relationships that is believable (this movie does not.) <br /><br />Sure Tristan is drawn away from his family but why was that again? what's the deal with his father again that he has to ask permission to go out at his age? interesting picture though to ask about the lack and need of rebellious behavior of kids in upper class family. But this movie does not go in this direction. Even though there would be the potential judging by the random Backflashes. Wasn't he already down and out, why does he do it again? <br /><br />So there are some interesting questions brought up here for a solid socially critic drama (but then again, this movie is just not, because of focusing on "cool" production techniques and special effects an not giving the characters a moment to reflect and most of all forcing the story along the path where they want it to be and not paying attention to let the story breath and naturally evolve.) <br /><br />It wants to be a drama to not glorify abuse of substances and violence (would be political incorrect these days, wouldn't it?) but on the other hand it is nothing more then a cheap action movie (like there are so so many out there) with an average set of actors and a <PERSON>Vinnie Jones</PERSON> who is managing to not totally ruin what's left of his reputation by doing what he always does.<br /><br />So all in all i .. just ... can't recommend it.<br /><br />1 for <PERSON>Vinnie</PERSON> and 2 for the editing.
15 1 Although I didn't like <ORGANIZATION>Stanley & Iris</ORGANIZATION> tremendously as a film, I did admire the acting. <PERSON>Jane Fonda</PERSON> and <PERSON>Robert De Niro</PERSON> are great in this movie. I haven't always been a fan of <PERSON>Fonda</PERSON>'s work but here she is delicate and strong at the same time. <PERSON>De Niro</PERSON> has the ability to make every role he portrays into acting gold. He gives a great performance in this film and there is a great scene where he has to take his father to a home for elderly people because he can't care for him anymore that will break your heart. I wouldn't really recommend this film as a great cinematic entertainment, but I will say you won't see much bette acting anywhere.
16 0 6/10 Acting, not great but some good acting.<br /><br />4/10 Director, makes some stupid decisions for this film.<br /><br />2/10 Writer, story makes no sense at all and has huge amount of flaws.<br /><br />4/10 Overall score for this movie.<br /><br />Don't waste your time with this film, it's not worth it. I gave 4 for this movie and it may be too much. Characters are so over exaggerated than they can ever be in real life and some pretty unexplainable stuff happens "storywise", not in good way. Because of the style this film has been filmed you get bored after 30 minutes (too many special effects: slow motions and camera shakes and fast forwards). It's always good that movie uses music to make the story go smooth but there's too many tracks in this one. In the first hour there is almost 50/50 dialogs and musics
17 1 Very good drama although it appeared to have a few blank areas leaving the viewers to fill in the action for themselves. I can imagine life being this way for someone who can neither read nor write. This film simply smacked of the real world: the wife who is suddenly the sole supporter, the live-in relatives and their quarrels, the troubled child who gets knocked up and then, typically, drops out of school, a jackass husband who takes the nest egg and buys beer with it. 2 thumbs up.
18 0 This is one of the dumbest films, I've ever seen. It rips off nearly ever type of thriller and manages to make a mess of them all.<br /><br />There's not a single good line or character in the whole mess. If there was a plot, it was an afterthought and as far as acting goes, there's nothing good to say so Ill say nothing. I honestly cant understand how this type of nonsense gets produced and actually released, does somebody somewhere not at some stage think, 'Oh my god this really is a load of shite' and call it a day. Its crap like this that has people downloading illegally, the trailer looks like a completely different film, at least if you have download it, you haven't wasted your time or money Don't waste your time, this is painful.
19 1 Working-class romantic drama from director <PERSON>Martin Ritt</PERSON> is as unbelievable as they come, yet there are moments of pleasure due mostly to the charisma of stars <PERSON>Jane Fonda</PERSON> and <PERSON>Robert De Niro</PERSON> (both terrific). She's a widow who can't move on, he's illiterate and a closet-inventor--you can probably guess the rest. Adaptation of <PERSON>Pat Barker</PERSON>'s novel "Union Street" (a better title!) is so laid-back it verges on bland, and the film's editing is a mess, but it's still pleasant; a rosy-hued blue-collar fantasy. There are no overtures to serious issues (even the illiteracy angle is just a plot-tool for the ensuing love story) and no real fireworks, though the characters are intentionally a bit colorless and the leads are toned down to an interesting degree. The finale is pure fluff--and cynics will find it difficult to swallow--though these two characters deserve a happy ending and the picture wouldn't really be satisfying any other way. *** from ****
20 0 This film had a lot of promise, and the plot was relatively interesting, however the actors, director and editors seriously let this film down.<br /><br />I feel bad for the writers, it could have been good. The acting is wooden, very few of the characters are believable.<br /><br />Who ever edited this clearly just learnt some new edit techniques and wanted to splash them all over the film. There are lots of quick 'flashy' edits in almost every scene, which are clearly meant to be symbolic but just end up as annoying.<br /><br />I wanted to like this film and expected there to be a decent resolution to the breakdown of equilibrium but alas no, it left me feeling like I'd wasted my time and the film makers had wasted their money.
21 1 I'm a male, not given to women's movies, but this is really a well done special story. I have no personal love for <PERSON>Jane Fonda</PERSON> as a person but she does one Hell of a fine job, while <PERSON>DeNiro</PERSON> is his usual superb self. Everything is so well done: acting, directing, visuals, settings, photography, casting. If you can enjoy a story of real people and real love - this is a winner.
22 0 If you look at <PERSON>Corey Large</PERSON>'s information here on IMDb, apparently there's a movie called "Reload" in production (as of June '08) in which he's playing a character named <PERSON>Sebastian Cole</PERSON>.<br /><br />First of all, how does such a crappy movie ever earn a sequel ... and second, didn't <PERSON>Sebastian</PERSON> get killed at the end of "Loaded"?<br /><br />I watched this in the wee hours of the morning when I was battling insomnia, and so I was drifting in and out while it was on. I'm sure I missed some plot points, but overall, it seemed really weak. Large's performance was (for me) one of the stronger parts of the film. I'm also a bit surprised at all the people commenting on the beautiful girls, since I thought the actress playing <PERSON>Brooke</PERSON> was pretty, but not exceptional.
23 1 <ORGANIZATION>Liked Stanley & Iris</ORGANIZATION> very much. Acting was very good. Story had a unique and interesting arrangement. The absence of violence and porno sex was refreshing. Characters were very convincing and felt like you could understand their feelings. Very enjoyable movie.
24 0 All I could think of while watching this movie was B-grade slop. Many have spoken about it's redeeming quality is how this film portrays such a realistic representation of the effects of drugs and an individual and their subsequent spiral into a self perpetuation state of unfortunate events. Yet really, the techniques used (as many have already mentioned) were overused and thus unconvincing and irrelevant to the film as a whole.<br /><br />As far as the plot is concerned, it was lacklustre, unimaginative, implausible and convoluted. You can read most other reports on this film and they will say pretty much the same as I would.<br /><br />Granted some of the actors and actresses are attractive but when confronted with such boring action... looks can only carry a film so far. The action is poor and intermittent: a few punches thrown here and there, and a final gunfight towards the end. Nothing really to write home about.<br /><br />As others have said, 'BAD' movies are great to watch for the very reason that they are 'bad', you revel in that fact. This film, however, is a void. It's nothing.<br /><br />Furthermore, if one is really in need of an educational movie to scare people away from drug use then I would seriously recommend any number of other movies out there that board such issues in a much more effective way. 'Requiem For A Dream', 'Trainspotting', 'Fear and Loathing in <LOCATION>Las Vegas</LOCATION>' and <ORGANIZATION>'Candy</ORGANIZATION>' are just a few examples. Though one should also check out some more lighthearted films on the same subject like 'Go' (overall, both serious and funny) and 'Halfbaked'.<br /><br />On a final note, the one possibly redeeming line in this movie, delivered by <PERSON>Vinnie Jones</PERSON> was stolen from 'Lock, Stock and Two Smokling Barrels'. To think that a bit of that great movie has been tainted by 'Loaded' is vile.<br /><br />Overall, I strongly suggest that you save you money and your time by NOT seeing this movie.
25 1 <ORGANIZATION>Liked Stanley & Iris</ORGANIZATION> very much. Acting was very good. Story had a unique and interesting arrangement. The absence of violence and sex was refreshing. Characters were very convincing and felt like you could understand their feelings. Very enjoyable movie.
26 0 Weak plot, predictable violence, only semi interesting characters. Like the writer (also one of the stars?) was fictionalizing his own screw ups and added an incredulous fantasies of drugs and murder to make it "hot". From the predictable rap and house soundtrack, to the family conflicts, it's poorly acted, stereotypical, and ultimately terribly boring. Even the title has been done before - IMDb lists FIVE movies with the same name released in 2007-2008!! <br /><br />Note: Saw it on <ORGANIZATION>Showtime</ORGANIZATION>, which listed the synopsis for one of the other movies. Was halfway thru before I realized no one was an undercover cop. Even tho another stereotype, would have made it interesting if it happened.
27 1 The production quality, cast, premise, authentic <LOCATION>New England</LOCATION> (<LOCATION>Waterbury</LOCATION>, CT?) locale and lush <PERSON>John Williams</PERSON> score should have resulted in a 3-4 star collectors item. Unfortunately, all we got was a passable 2 star "decent" flick, mostly memorable for what it tried to do.........bring an art house style film mainstream. The small town locale and story of ordinary people is a genre to itself, and if well done, will satisfy most grownups. <PERSON>Jane Fonda</PERSON> was unable to hide her braininess enough to make her character believable. I wondered why she wasn't doing a post doctorate at <ORGANIZATION>Yale</ORGANIZATION> instead of working in a dead end factory job in <LOCATION>Waterbury</LOCATION>. <PERSON>Robert DiNiro</PERSON>'s character was just a bit too contrived. An illiterate, nice guy loser who turns out to actually be, with a little help from <PERSON>Jane</PERSON>'s character, a 1990 version of <PERSON>Henry Ford</PERSON> or <PERSON>Thomas Edison</PERSON>.<br /><br />This genre has been more successfully handled by "Nobody's Fool" in the mid 90s and this year's (2003) "About <PERSON>Schmidt</PERSON>." I wish that the main stream studios would try more stuff for post adolescents and reserve a couple of screens at the multi cinema complexes for those efforts.<br /><br />I'll give it an "A" for effort.
28 0 There are times when finishing a film one wishes to have a refund for the time just spent. This was one of those times. I almost gave up with only 15 minutes left to endure... and I wish I had...<br /><br />The pace that a man goes from a straight-laced, controlled life to one of complete spinelessness and irresponsibility could never be this rapid.<br /><br />From a graduation celebration to the predictable ending Tristan Price (<PERSON>Jesse Metcalfe</PERSON>) man of privilege and culture allows himself to be seduced by a woman, by violence, and by mind altering substances. Of course, the woman part is understandable when observing the talents of the beautiful April (<PERSON>Nathalie Kelley</PERSON>). But the in for a penny in for a pound aspect of the drugs, violence and dedication to a person he has just met is impossible to understand.<br /><br />Frankly, besides being able to stare at <PERSON>Nathalie Kelley</PERSON> and <PERSON>Monica Keena</PERSON>, this film has no redeeming qualities. Save your money, save your time... do anything else...
29 1 This film has a special place in my heart, as when I caught it the first time, I was teaching adult literacy. It rang very true to me and even an outstanding student I had at the time. There are scenes which make you gulp with sudden emotion, and those which even put a smile on your face through sheer identification with the characters and their situation. <br /><br />Excellent performances by <PERSON>Jane Fonda</PERSON> and <PERSON>Robert DeNiro</PERSON> that rank with their best work, a great turn by a young <PERSON>Martha Plimpton</PERSON>, an inspiring story line, and a haunting musical score makes for a most enjoyable and rewarding experience.
30 0 This is it. This is the one. This is the worst movie ever made. Ever. It beats everything. I have never seen worse. Retire the trophy and give it to these people.....there's just no comparison.<br /><br />Even three days after watching this (for some reason I still don't know why) I cannot believe how insanely horrific this movie is/was. Its so bad. So far from anything that could be considered a movie, a story or anything that should have ever been created and brought into our existence.<br /><br />This made me question whether or not humans are truly put on this earth to do good. It made me feel disgusted with ourselves and our progress as a species in this universe. This type of movie sincerely hurts us as a society. We should be ashamed. I really cannot emphasize that our global responsibility as people living here and creating art, is that we need to prevent the creation of these gross distortions of our reality for our own good. It's an embarrassment. I don't know how on earth any of these actors, writers, or the director of this film sleeps at night knowing that they had a role in making "Loaded". I don't know what type of disgusting monsters enjoy watching these types of movies.<br /><br />That being said, I love a good "bad" movie. I love Shark Attack 3, I love Bad Taste, they are HILARIOUS. I tell all my friends to see them because they are "bad".<br /><br />But this.......this crosses the line of "bad" into a whole new dimension. This is awkward bad. This is the bad where you know everything that is going to happen, every line, every action, every death, every sequence BEFORE they happen; and not just like a second or two before, I mean like, after watching the first 5 minutes before.<br /><br />Every cheesy editing "effect" is shamelessly used over and over again to a sickening point. I really never want to see the "shaky" camera "drug buzz rush" effect or jump cuts or swerve cuts or ANY FANCY CUT EVER AGAIN EVER. This is meticulously boring, repetitive and just tortures the audience.<br /><br />But.......and let me be specific here, the most DISTURBING thing about this movie is that given the production, it appears that a somewhat decent amount of money was actually put into this excrement. I personally will grab the shoulders of the director if I ever see him and shake him into submission, demanding that he run home and swallow two-gallons of Drain-O or I will do it for him.<br /><br />If we ever needed a new form of inhumane torture for our war prisoners abroad, just keep showing them this movie in a padded cell over and over again. Trust me, I think they will become more extravagant with suicide methods after the 72nd time of sitting through this.<br /><br />Stop these movies, they are just the most vile of all facets of our society. Please. Stop. NOW.
31 1 I guess if a film has magic, I don't need it to be fluid or seamless. It can skip background information, go too fast in some places, too slow in others, etc. Magic in this film: the scene in the library. There are many minor flaws in <ORGANIZATION>Stanley & Iris</ORGANIZATION>, yet they don't detract from the overall positive impact of watching people help each other in areas of life that seem the most incomprehensible, the hardest to fix. Both characters are smart. Yet <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> can't understand enough to function because he can't read; he can't read because he's had too much adventure in his childhood. <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>, although well-educated, hasn't had enough adventure and so can't understand how to move past the U-turn her life took. In both their faults and strengths, the characters compliment each other. It may be a bit of a stretch to accept that an <PERSON>Iris</PERSON> would wind up working year after year in a factory, or that a <ORGANIZATION>Stanley</ORGANIZATION> never hid his illiteracy enough to work in construction or some other better-paying job. And while these "mysteries" are explained in the course of the story, their unfolding seems somewhat contrived. I assume no one took the time to rethink the script. Even so, it's a good movieÂ—just imagine what <PERSON>De Niro</PERSON>, <PERSON>Fonda</PERSON> and <PERSON>Plimpton</PERSON> would have done on screen if someone had!
32 0 There are lots of extremely good-looking people in this movie. That's probably the best thing about it. Perhaps that even makes it worth watching.<br /><br />"Loaded" tells the story of Tristan Price (<PERSON>Jesse Metcalfe</PERSON>), a young man who's about to make his mark on the world. He's the son of a well-to-do family with a good reputation, and he's on his way to law school. But like so many such settings, things aren't quite as perfect as they appear. The expectations in this family far outweigh the love. Except for school, Tristan's father rarely lets him leave the house. This seems to be the result of some past traumatic event that shook the family, which is partially revealed through flashbacks but isn't spelled out until the very end. Tristan's claustrophobic environment causes him to let loose in very extreme ways at the first possible opportunity, when his friends take him out to a strip club to celebrate his graduation. The celebration soon follows some strippers back to a beach house party, and from there, Tristan befriends <PERSON>Sebastian Cole</PERSON> (<PERSON>Corey Large</PERSON>), who pulls him into a drug dealing underworld.<br /><br />While technically well-made, this movie suffers from a lackluster script and a storyline that isn't very engaging. Also counting against this film are some constant camera tricks that generally seemed annoying and out-of-place, such as slow-motion, fast-motion, freeze-frames and echos. These are the types of effects a director might normally utilize to show a character's perspective while on drugs, except in this case they seem to have been sporadically tossed in at random points, in some cheap attempt at style.<br /><br />Despite its cast of relative unknowns, performances were good all around, most notably with respect to the main antagonist (<PERSON>Corey Large</PERSON>). I suspect we'll be seeing at least a couple of these people in bigger and better projects in the future.<br /><br />Of course, when mentioning the actors, I must mention their looks. Rating based on hotness, this movies scores an 11. The women in this movie are incredible-looking and almost distract you from what a boring movie you're watching. I'm sure the male characters are also quite attractive, but you'll have to ask someone else to comment on that.<br /><br />Overall, I can't recommend this movie, not for buying, renting, or even seeing for free. It's unfortunately just not worth the effort it takes to sit through.
33 1 I found this to be a so-so romance/drama that has a nice ending and a generally nice feel to it. It's not a Hallmark Hall Of Fame-type family film with sleeping-before-marriage considered "normal" behavior but considering it stars <PERSON>Jane Fonda</PERSON> and <PERSON>Robert De Niro</PERSON>, I would have expected a lot rougher movie, at least language-wise. <br /><br />The most memorable part of the film is the portrayal of how difficult it must be to learn how to read and write when you are already an adult. That's the big theme of the movie and it involves some touching scenes but, to be honest, the film isn't that memorable.<br /><br />It's still a fairly mild, nice tale that I would be happy to recommend.
34 0 Nine minutes of psychedelic, pulsating, often symmetric abstract images, are enough to drive anyone crazy. I did spot a full-frame eye at the start, and later some birds silhouetted against other colors. It was just not my cup of tea. It's about 8Â½ minutes too long.
35 1 This is a complex film that explores the effects of Fordist and Taylorist modes of industrial capitalist production on human relations. There are constant references to assembly line production, where workers are treated as cogs in a machine, overseen by managers wielding clipboards, controlling how much hair the workers leave exposed, and firing workers (<ORGANIZATION>Stanley</ORGANIZATION>) who meet all criteria (as his supervisor says, are always on time, are hard workers, do good work) but who may in some unspecified future make a mistake. <br /><br />This system destroys families - <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> has to send his father to a nursing home (where he quickly dies) after <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> loses his job. <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>' daughter is a single teen mother who drops out of high school to take a job in the plant. References are made to the fact that now, with declining wages, both partners need to work, the implication being that there's nobody left at home to care for the kids. <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>' husband is dead from an illness, and with the multiple references in the film about the costs of medical care, the viewer must wonder if he might have lived with better and more costly care. <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>' brother in law gets abusive after yet another unsuccessful day at the unemployment office when his wife yells at him for buying a beer with her savings instead of leaving it for her face lift and/or teeth job (even the working class with no stake in conventional bourgeois notions of perfection and beauty buy into them). The one reference to race in the film is through a black factory line worker whose husband is in jail (presumably, he's also black, and black men suffer disproportionally high incarceration rates). She remarks that he, like her, "is doing time" - her family is composed of a prisoner and a wage slave.<br /><br /><PERSON>Stanley</PERSON>, however, still believes in human relations and is therefore for most of the film outside of the system of Fordist capitalism. He cares for his father in spite of the fact that it was his father's traveling salesman job that resulted in his illiteracy - he has not yet reduced human relations to a purely instrumental contract, as Iris' brother in law does (suggesting that he "married the wrong sister"). He does not, as <PERSON>Iris</PERSON> says, conform to the work-eat-sleep routine of everyone else; rather, he uses technology and the techniques of industrial production in an artisanal and creative way, in a sort of Bauhaus ideal. This was the dream of early modernists and 1920's socialists (such as the Bauhaus) - to use technology to provide for all basic needs, allowing for more free time for creative human work and fuller human relations. He is also outside of traditional gender relations. He cooks, he cleans, he cares for his family, and he knows how to iron. <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>, on the other hand, lives in a traditionally male role - she's a factory worker, the mains source of income for her (extended) family, and she brings <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> into the public realm, traditionally off-limits to women. By teaching him to read and write, she gives him access to the world of knowledge, also traditionally gendered male.<br /><br />Literacy here is used as a metaphor for the (traditionally masculine) public realm and the systems of circulation (monetary, vehicular, cultural) that enable participation in the public realm. Without this access, <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> is feminized - the jobs open to him are cooking and cleaning. He is excluded from all regular circulations, unable to participate in the monetary (can't open a bank account), in the vehicular (can't get a driver's license, can't ride the bus), and in the social (he asks if he exists if he can't write his name).<br /><br />After learning to read, he grabs books on auto repair, farming, and spirituality (the Bible). The Word of God is therefore relativized, placed on the same value plane as how-to books. In fact, organized religion in general is only very occasionally present - the Bible also appears on a dresser as the camera pans to find <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> and <PERSON>Iris</PERSON> having sex. It is, however, acknowledged as a moral force - <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>, clearly a character devoted to living a "good" life, mentions at the beginning of the film that her rosary was among the objects lost in a purse snatching.<br /><br />Once able to read, he enters the system and lands a managerial position with a health care plan, a car, and a house, taking his place at the head of the family, the breadwinner. Presumably, he's an industrial designer, dreaming up products that will require others enduring the drudgery of the assembly line to produce. This ending, probably the only bit of conventional <LOCATION>Hollywood</LOCATION> in the film, is so incongruous with all that has come before that I at least wonder if it wasn't forced in by some Studio exec suddenly worried about the lack of a feel-good ending and its potential effect on the bottom line.<br /><br />Now that, according to the pundits, we've comfortably moved on to post-industrial capitalism, the film also has a slightly nostalgic feel, as though we needed the historical distance to really analyze what happened during that period. <br /><br />Nevertheless, it's highly recommended - at least if you want to exercise your brain. Disregard the ending, and it's close to a perfect 10.
36 0 This is an art film that was either made in 1969 or 1972 (the <ORGANIZATION>National Film Preservation Foundation</ORGANIZATION> says 1969 and <ORGANIZATION>IMDb</ORGANIZATION> says 1972). Regardless of the exact date, the film definitely appears to be very indicative of this general time period--with some camera-work and pop art stylings that are pure late 60s-early 70s.<br /><br />The film consists of three simple images that are distorted using different weird camera tricks. These distorted images are accompanied by music and there is absolutely no dialog or plot of any sort. This was obviously intended as almost like a form of performance art, and like most performance art, it's interesting at first but quickly becomes tiresome. The film, to put it even more bluntly, is a total bore and would appeal to no one but perhaps those who made the film, their family and friends and perhaps a few people just too hip and "with it" to be understood by us mortals.
37 1 `<PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> and <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>' is a heart warming film about two people who find each other and help one another overcome their problems in life. <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON>'s life is difficult, because he never learned to read or write. <PERSON>Iris</PERSON> is a widower with two teenage children working in a bakery where she meets <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON>. She decides to teach <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> how to read at her home in her spare time. Over time they become romantically involved. After <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> learns to read, he goes off to a good job in <LOCATION>Chicago</LOCATION>, only to return to <PERSON>Iris</PERSON> and ask her to marry him.<br /><br />It's a really good film without nudity, violence, or profanity, that which is rare in today's films. A good film all round. <br /><br />
38 0 I am a big fan of <PERSON>Arnold Vosloo</PERSON>. Finally seeing him as the star of a recent movie, not just a bit part, made me happy.<br /><br />Unfortunately I took film appreciation in college and the only thing I can say that I didn't like was that the film was made in an abandoned part of town and there was no background traffic or lookie loos.<br /><br />I have to say that the acting leaves something to be desired, but <PERSON>Arnold</PERSON> is an excellent actor, I have to chalk it up to lousy direction and the supporting cast leaves something to be desired.<br /><br />I love <PERSON>Arnold Vosloo</PERSON>, and he made the film viewable. Otherwise, I would have written it off as another lousy film.<br /><br />I found the rape scene brutal and unnecessary, but the actors that got away at the end were pretty good. But the sound effects of the shoot-out were pretty bad. There are some glitches in the film (continuity) but they are overlookable considering the low-caliber of the film.<br /><br />All in all I enjoyed the film, because <PERSON>Arnold Vosloo</PERSON> was in it.<br /><br /><PERSON>Jackie</PERSON>
39 1 I just read the comments of TomReynolds2004 and feel I have to jump in here. I understand he doesn't like the film, but his reasons are not evident. My feeling regarding this film is that it is not afraid to travel the darker roads of loneliness, failure, disappointment and sorrow. Each of these two people, as portrayed, have plenty of reasons to be bitter and angry, yet find tenderness and comfort in each the other. Only great acting could make this work without becoming an emotional quagmire, sentimental and sappy. I really became interested in these people because of their overwhelming humanity given to them by such strong performances. I have every reason to dislike <PERSON>Jane Fonda</PERSON> for her <LOCATION>Vietnam</LOCATION> era actions, but personal feelings apart, she is fabulous in this role. <PERSON>Robert DeNiro</PERSON> is superb as a man whose intelligence and goodness begins to fail him in a world indifferent to his abilities. This is the first I have seen <PERSON>DeNiro</PERSON> using tenderness rather than toughness to sell a character and I really like it. This film was a big surprise when I first viewed it and I look forward to seeing it again.
40 0 This movie was terrible. at first i just read the plot summary and it looked OK, so i watched it. The acting was TERRIBLE. it was like the actor were almost camera shy. everything seemed fake. i feel bad for <PERSON>Edward Furlong</PERSON>, terminator 2 was my favorite a few years ago.. I've watched it at least 20 times....<br /><br />the plot was also crap. the writers were probably sleep deprived when they came up with the lines.<br /><br />on the plus side, it's the good kind of bad movie. the one you keep watching just to see how much worst could it will get, so that later you can tell other people how you couldn't believe how terrible the movie was.<br /><br />i think everybody should watch this, so that then we could appreciate better other, REAL, movies.
41 1 '<PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> and <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>' show the triumph of the human spirit. For <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON>, it's the struggle to become literate and realize his potential. For <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>, it's to find the courage to love again after becoming a widow. The beauty of the movie is the dance that <PERSON>Robert DeNiro</PERSON> and <PERSON>Jane Fonda</PERSON> do together, starting and stopping, before each has the skills and courage to completely trust each other and move on. In that sense it very nicely gives us a good view of how life often is, thus being credible. Unlike some other reviewers I found the characters each rendered to be consistent for the whole picture. The supporting cast is also carefully chosen and they add a depth of character that the main characters get added meaning from the supporting performances. All in all an excellent movie. The best thing I take from it is Hope.
42 0 What was with all the Turkish actors? No offense but I thought it was all for nothing for all these actors. The film had no script to test any actors acting skill or ability. It demanded next to nothing I bought this film to see <PERSON>Michael Madsen</PERSON>. He is one of my favorite actors but this film was another failure for him. The script was so bad. Their was just nothing to sink your teeth into and all the characters were two dimensional. <PERSON>Madsen</PERSON> tried to act like a hard ass but the script and direction didn't even allow him to do enough with his character to make it more interesting or 3 dimensional.<br /><br />Even the sound effects of the gunfight at the beginning of the film sounded like the noise of paint ball guns when they are fired in a skirmish. It was really weird and they didn't sound like real guns. A video game had better sound effects than this film. There was also a really annoying bloke at the beginning of the film who was a member of the robbery gang. He had this American whining voice like a girl shouting lines like "Lets get the F#$k out of here" and What are we going to do man". He sounded like a girl. As a positive It was funny to watch and it made me laugh too. For a few seconds. Whoo <PERSON>Hoo</PERSON> ! Dumb Film. Poor <PERSON>Madsen</PERSON>. He will bounce back...
43 1 This may not be a memorable classic, but it is a touching romance with an important theme that stresses the importance of literacy in modern society and the devastating career and life consequences for any unfortunate individual lacking this vital skill.<br /><br />The story revolves around <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>, a widow who becomes acquainted with a fellow employee at her factory job, an illiterate cafeteria worker named <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON>. <PERSON>Iris</PERSON> discovers that <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON> is unable to read, and after he loses his job, she gives him reading lessons at home in her kitchen. Of course, as you might predict, the two, although initially wary of involvement, develop feelings for each other...<br /><br /><PERSON>Jane Fonda</PERSON> competently plays <PERSON>Iris</PERSON>, a woman with problems of her own, coping with a job lacking prospects, two teenage children (one pregnant), an unemployed sister and her abusive husband. However, <PERSON>Robert DeNiro</PERSON> is of course brilliant in his endearing portrayal of the intelligent and resourceful, but illiterate, <PERSON>Stanley</PERSON>, bringing a dignity to the role that commands respect. They aren't your typical charming young yuppie couple, as generally depicted in on screen romances, but an ordinary working class, middle aged pair with pretty down to earth struggles.<br /><br />I won't give the ending away, but it's a lovely, heartwarming romance and a personal look into the troubling issue of adult illiteracy, albeit from the perspective of a fictional character.
44 0 I saw this DVD in my friends house and thought that this was a Turkish action movie with some Hollywood-not very big-names in it. Interested enough I decide to give it a shot later.. It was a tough to bear experience believe me. Then, after finally seeing the credits roll I tought 'We Turks really suck at <LOCATION>Hollywood</LOCATION> style film making.. This is an insult to the heist|hostage movie genre..' but then wait! I checked some names and no, they were not Turkish names and no, this was not a Turkish movie; on the contrary it was literally shot in <LOCATION>America</LOCATION> with an American director & crew! That made me thinking-again!- How on earth can you persuade names like <PERSON>Micheal Madsen</PERSON>, <PERSON>Edward Furlong</PERSON> or even <PERSON>Arnold Vosloo</PERSON> to take part in such a project? with money probably.. That kept me thinking further.. How can you raise such amount of money to offer them and a supposedly international cast? Then all my meditation paid off and I came to find the answer.By hiring the cheapest equipment and crew that you can find. And if you still have to difficulty in adjustin your budget then: by writing and directing the movie you are trying to produce-or vice versa I don't have any information on that-. So bottom line this is not a bad movie as everybody are so anxious to present as.. It makes you think -in my case even meditate- and there are a lot of movies outthere that doesn't give even that affect.. This one at least makes you think; It makes you wonder.. It leaves you with disbelief.. and then It makes you wonder again..
45 1 If you fast forward through the horrible singing, you will find a classic fairy tale underneath. <PERSON>Christopher Walken</PERSON> is very humorous and surprisingly good in the role. His trademark style of acting works well for the sly Puss in Boots. The other actors are well for their parts. I did not find any of the acting terribly fake or awkward. The king in particular appears a real dunce though, and I wonder if he is supposed to be. I can not remember the original tale. The special effects are typical of the eighties, but at least they are not overly fake like some of the computer generated fare that we see today. Overall, I recommend this movie for children and adults who are a child at heart.
46 0 I rented this one on DVD without any prior knowledge. I was suspicious seeing <PERSON>Michael Madsen</PERSON> appearing in a movie I have never heard of, but it was a freebie, so why not check it out.<br /><br />Well my guess is that Mr. <PERSON>Blonde</PERSON> would very much like to forget he's ever taken part in such a shame of a film.<br /><br />Apparently, if your script and dialogs are terrible, even good actors cannot save the day. Not to mention the amateur actors that flood this film. Too many non-native-English-speakers play parts of native-English-speakers, reading out lines from a script that should have been thrown away and not having been made into a movie. It's unbelievable how unbelievable all the lines in the movie sound. The music is awful and totally out of place, and the whole thing looks and sounds like a poor school play.<br /><br />I recommend you watch it just so you would appreciate other, better, movies. This is why I gave it a 3 instead of the 1 it deserves.
47 1 OK, so the musical pieces were poorly written and generally poorly sung (though <PERSON>Walken</PERSON> and <PERSON>Marner</PERSON>, particularly <PERSON>Walken</PERSON>, sounded pretty good). And so they shattered the fourth wall at the end by having the king and his nobles sing about the "battle" with the ogre, and praise the efforts of Puss in Boots when they by rights shouldn't have even known about it.<br /><br />Who cares? It's <PERSON>Christopher Freakin</PERSON>' <PERSON>Walken</PERSON>, doing a movie based on a fairy tale, and he sings and dances. His acting style fits the role very well as the devious, mischievous Puss who seems to get his master into deeper and deeper trouble but in fact has a plan he's thought about seven or eight moves in advance. And if you've ever seen <PERSON>Walken</PERSON> in any of his villainous roles, you *know* the ogre bit the dust HARD at the end when <PERSON>Walken</PERSON> got him into his trap.<br /><br />A fun film, and a must-see for anyone who enjoys the unique style of <PERSON>Christopher Walken</PERSON>.
48 0 I have to congratulate the genius who approved this one. <PERSON>Edward Furlong</PERSON>, you're not as good as you think mate, you can't grab on every piece of low-cost amateur crap, which sole intention has to be to get some bucks.<br /><br />The filming is bad, and I mean BAD. Anyone with a camera would get the same result, or better.<br /><br />The acting, lets just say: don't go to the supermarket looking for actors. The good ones usually come with a degree or, at least, have some damn experience! The director.. Mr. <PERSON>Jon Keeyes</PERSON>, please find your purpose in life, as a director you simply suck. Your directing is poor, the angles are all messed up (not in a good way), the lines seem as if they're being read out of toilet paper, and the damn music.. it always comes up when it shouldn't and goes out for no apparent reason. And don't go for writer either, by the way. Making movies isn't like serving on a coffeshop, it requires art and skill, things I really doubt you'll ever have.<br /><br />Instead of making a badass shootout movie, you should've shot this one back to oblivion and wait 'till something good came up.. Or just go find a job on a coffeshop. You'll have less stress and you'll save movie goers some money and a bad night.<br /><br />vote: 1/10 (my first one)
49 1 Although this was obviously a low-budget production, the performances and the songs in this movie are worth seeing. One of <PERSON>Walken</PERSON>'s few musical roles to date. (he is a marvelous dancer and singer and he demonstrates his acrobatic skills as well - watch for the cartwheel!) Also starring <PERSON>Jason Connery</PERSON>. A great children's story and very likable characters.
50 0 Sometimes a movie is so comprehensively awful it has a destructive effect on your morale. You begin to really ask yourself, what does it mean for our society that the standard is so terribly low? Can they honestly expect that we'll endure this many clichÃ©s and still be entertained?<br /><br />Of course, it is still a <LOCATION>Hollywood</LOCATION> mainstay to make the GUN the major character, plot device, and the source of all conflict and resolution in films. Character needs a gun. Gets a gun. Can't do that because he has a gun. Puts his gun down first. OH MY GOD What are we going to do!? He has a gun! He waves it around, acting more malicious than real human beings ever do. He pushes it in someone's face for 90 minutes, shouting questions. The hallmark of any conclusion will be the comforting sound of police sirens. <br /><br />It's a real challenge to make such a tired, hackneyed formula work again; a film has to be very clever and well executed. This one is neither. It has no life and no personality, and it will suck these components from YOU. it will make you feel WORSE about living in the time and space that you do. Really, who needs that!? So yes, I'll say it: I think this may well be the worst film I have ever seen. Anyone who was involved in the making of this sub- mediocre soul killing trash should be publicly embarrassed for the disservice they've done to us all.
51 1 I never saw this when I was a kid, so this was seen with fresh eyes. I had never heard of it and rented it for my 5 year old daughter. Plus, the idea of <PERSON>Christopher Walken</PERSON> singing and dancing made me curious. The special fx are cheesy and the singing and dancing is mediocre. But the story is great. My daughter was entranced. I loved watching <PERSON>Walken</PERSON> in this role thinking about what the future held for him. Very amusing to see him dance! And if the songs weren't great, at least they weren't <ORGANIZATION>Disney</ORGANIZATION> over-produced saccharine sweetness. The ogre scene in the beginning was a little scary for her, and she was a little nervous when we saw him again at the end, but it was mostly benign. Interestingly, we had recently read "Puss in Boots", and I had wondered about the implausibility of the story. But while staying true to almost every aspect, <PERSON>Walken</PERSON>'s acting made it believable. Great fun. I'd watch it again with my daughter.
52 0 Assuming this won't end up a straight-to-video release, I would have to say void this title at all costs. Unless you're bored of good, well-executed movies, that is. I saw this last night at <ORGANIZATION>AFI</ORGANIZATION> <LOCATION>Dallas</LOCATION>, and I left with 20 minutes remaining, simply because I didn't care anymore (about the plot, not about insulting the director...that is awkward). When you can spot a goof only 5 minutes into the movie (a shot out, shattered window before any shots are fired...and then the window breaks with the first shot), things are going to bad. Let's just say this is only an indicator of things to come...unfortunately.<br /><br />I'll spare you all the details, but this is sub-par in every manner, even the half-assed acting by <PERSON>Michael Madsen</PERSON> is disappointing when you're expecting half-assed acting from him. And the rape scene...Christ! "Shut up and take it" should never be used in a rape scene. EVER.<br /><br />3/10
53 1 When I was a kid I watched this many times over, and I remember whistling the "Happy Cat" song quite often. All the songs are great, and actually memorable, unlike many children's musicals, where the songs are just stuck in for no real reason. The scenes and costumes are lavish, and the acting is very well-done, which isn't surprising, considering the cast. <PERSON>Christopher Walken</PERSON> is very catlike, and doesn't need stupid make-up, or a cat costume for the viewer to believe he's a cat transformed to a human. And <PERSON>Jason Connery</PERSON>'s so cute, as the shy and awkward miller's son, <PERSON>Corin</PERSON>, who falls in love with beautiful and the bold Princess <PERSON>Vera</PERSON>. This is a really fun, enjoyable, feature-length movie, where unlike most fairytales, the characters are given personalities. Some of my favourite parts are when <PERSON>Puss</PERSON> makes <PERSON>Corin</PERSON> pretend he's drowning; at the ball when everybody starts dancing a country dance, as it's "all the rage abroad"; when <PERSON>Walken</PERSON> is in the kitchen, dancing on the table (he's a pretty good dancer, too!); and when <PERSON>Vera</PERSON> tells <PERSON>Corin</PERSON> all the things she used to do when she was young, like pretending she was a miller's daughter. I'd recommend this film to children and parents alike, who love magic and fairytales. And it actually IS a movie you can watch together, as it won't drive adults up the wall.
54 0 Terrible movie. <PERSON>Nuff Said</PERSON>.<br /><br />These Lines are Just Filler. The movie was bad. Why I have to expand on that I don't know. This is already a waste of my time. I just wanted to warn others. Avoid this movie. The acting sucks and the writing is just moronic. Bad in every way. The only nice thing about the movie are <PERSON>Deniz Akkaya</PERSON>'s breasts. Even that was ruined though by a terrible and unneeded rape scene. The movie is a poorly contrived and totally unbelievable piece of garbage.<br /><br />OK now I am just going to rag on IMDb for this stupid rule of 10 lines of text minimum. First I waste my time watching this offal. Then feeling compelled to warn others I create an account with IMDb only to discover that I have to write a friggen essay on the film just to express how bad I think it is. Totally unnecessary.
55 1 <PERSON>Emilio Miraglio</PERSON>'s "<ORGANIZATION>The Red Queen Kills Seven Times</ORGANIZATION>" (1972) is just about the most perfect example of a giallo that I have ever seen, mixing all the requisite elements into one sinister stew indeed. First of all, and of paramount importance for me, it has a complex, twisty plot that ultimately makes perfect sense, and the killer here does not come completely out of left field at the end. The story, concerning a series of gruesome murders (you already know how many from the film's title, right?) that takes place in seeming fulfillment of an ancient prophecy concerning two sisters, is an involving one, and the murderer, a red-cloaked figure with the insane laugh of a madwoman, is both frightening and memorable. Every great giallo requires some lovely lead actresses, and here we have quite an assortment, headed by the ridiculously beautiful <PERSON>Barbara Bouchet</PERSON> as one of the two sisters and, in one of her earlier roles, <PERSON>Sybil Danning</PERSON>, as a lustful tramp at <PERSON>Barbara</PERSON>'s fashion house. Another necessary ingredient of a superior giallo is a catchy, hummable score, and <PERSON>Bruno Nicolai</PERSON> provides one for this film that should stay with you for days. Gorgeous scenery? Check again. Filmed largely in <LOCATION>Wurzburg</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>Germany</LOCATION>, the picture is a treat for the eye indeed. OK, OK, but what about those murders? After all, isn't that what gialli are all about? Well, I'm pleased to report that most viewers should be well satisfied with the various knifings, shootings, impalements and other carnage that this film tastefully dishes out...not to mention the crypts, freaky dream sequence, rats and bats (and LOTS of 'em, too!), the drug references, a rape scene, the obligatory red herrings and, in the person of <PERSON>Ugo Pagliai</PERSON>, a hunky leading man for the female viewers. As I said, a perfect giallo. And even better, this DVD is from the fine folks at No Shame, and you know what that means: a gorgeous print and loads of extras, to boot! Thanks, guys!
56 0 This film is terrible. You don't really need to read this review further. If you are planning on watching it, suffice to say - don't (unless you are studying how not to make a good movie).<br /><br />The acting is horrendous... serious amateur hour. Throughout the movie I thought that it was interesting that they found someone who speaks and looks like <PERSON>Michael Madsen</PERSON>, only to find out that it is actually him! A new low even for him!!<br /><br />The plot is terrible. People who claim that it is original or good have probably never seen a decent movie before. Even by the standard of <LOCATION>Hollywood</LOCATION> action flicks, this is a terrible movie.<br /><br />Don't watch it!!! Go for a jog instead - at least you won't feel like killing yourself.
57 1 And here's yet another piece of evidence to claim that we should all worship the Italian giallo and acknowledge it to be the absolute most unique sub genre in horror. <PERSON>Emilio Miraglia</PERSON>'s "<ORGANIZATION>The Red Queen Kills Seven Times</ORGANIZATION>" is a totally mesmerizing wholesome of original plotting, stylish production values, enchanting music, great acting talents and inventively gory murder sequences. It's a fabulous giallo (released in the golden year 1972) that belongs in the top-five of every fan of Italian cinema. The storyline doesn't just introduce your average black-gloved & sexually frustrated killer, but blends good old-fashioned revenge motives with the macabre myth of the murderous "Red Queen". At young age, their grandfather tells the constantly fighting siblings <PERSON>Kitty</PERSON> and <PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON> about an uncanny lady who, once every 100 years on April 6th, kills seven people of which her sister is the inevitable last victim. Fourteen years later, <PERSON>Kitty</PERSON> has become the successful choreographer of a prominent modeling agency (even sharing her bed with the general manager) when suddenly the killing spree begins. Sister <PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON> would be the obvious culprit, but she moved to the <LOCATION>States</LOCATION> recently... Or has she? Complex yet compelling and involving red herrings are thrown at you every couple of minutes and the Red Queen character is definitely the most fascinating killer in giallo-history. Her face can never be seen, but she wears a blood red cloak and produces the most ghastly laugh whenever she made a new victim. She's not exactly gentle either, as her victims are barbarically stabbed with a dagger, dragged behind cars and even impaled on fences! That latter one is truly one of the greatest (= most gruesome) acts of violence I've ever seen! What more could you possibly request? Some classy and tasteful nudity, perhaps? The gorgeous female actresses got this more than covered, among them <PERSON>Barbara Bouchet</PERSON> and a young <PERSON>Sybil Danning</PERSON>. <PERSON>Emilio Miraglia</PERSON> isn't the most famous giallo-director, as he only made this one and the equally recommended "The Night Evelyn Came Out of the Grave", but his influence and importance should NOT be forgotten.
58 0 I cannot stay indifferent to <PERSON>Lars van Trier</PERSON>'s films. I consider 'Breaking the Waves' nothing less than a masterpiece. I loved 'Dancer in the Night'. I admired the idea in 'Dogville' but the overall exercise looked to me too dry and too theatrical, less cinema. 'Europa' which I see only now was a famous film at its time, succeeded in the <LOCATION>US</LOCATION> the relative success of an European film and got the Oscar for the best foreign language movie, but did not survive well the time in my opinion. It is also a too much explicit and extrovert exercise in cinema art to my taste.<br /><br />The story has a level of ambiguity that cannot escape the viewer. Treating the period that immediately followed the second world war not in the black and white colors of victors and vanquished, of executioners and victims but as rather ambiguous times when people of both sides were fighting for survival in the aftermath of a catastrophic event that change the lives of nations and individuals forever is still a source of disputes even today, more such was novel and courageous two decades ago. Yet it is the means of expression that really do not appear fit to the task.<br /><br />The film seems to include a lot of quotes descending directly from the films of <PERSON>Hitchcock</PERSON>, especially his early films set in the pre-war <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION>, with brave British spies fighting evil German spies on trains crossing at high speed the continent at dark. The trains were a symbol of the world and its conflicts with all their intensity and dramatism. Here the train also becomes the symbol of the first sparkles of the re-birth of <LOCATION>Germany</LOCATION> after war, of its might, of its obsession with order and regulation, of punctuality and civility. The characters that populate the train are far from being the classical spy stories good or bad guys. The principal character a young American of German origin coming to post-war <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION> willing to be part of a process of help and reconciliation finds himself in an ambiguous world of destruction and corruption, with liberators looking more like oppressive occupiers, with the vanquished not resigned to their fate but rather willing to continue on the path of self-destruction, with love doubtfully mixed with treason.<br /><br />It is yet this classical film treatment that betrays the director in this case. The actions of the characters, especially of <PERSON>Leopold Kessler</PERSON> played by <PERSON>Jean-Marc Barr</PERSON> seem confused, and lack credibility. The overall cinematography seems to be not Hitchcock-like but rather from a bad imitation of <PERSON>Hitchcock</PERSON> in the late 30s. The usage of color over the black-and-white film used in the majority of the time in moments of emotional intensity is also too demonstrative. It is not that <PERSON>Van Trier</PERSON> does not master his artistic means, but he is too demonstrative, he seems to try too hard to show what a great filmmaker he is. He really is great, as he will show in some of his later films, but it will be left to the viewers to decide this alone.
59 1 There are some films that every Horror fan owes himself (or herself) to see, and <PERSON>Emilio Miraglia</PERSON>'s "La Dama Rossa Uccide Sette Volte" aka. "The <ORGANIZATION>Red Queen Kills Seven Times</ORGANIZATION>" (1972) is definitely one of them. With <PERSON>Gialli</PERSON> and Gothic Tales being my two favorite sub-genres in Horror, I was looking forward to seeing this film for quite a while, and even though my expectations were high, this masterpiece surpassed my greatest hopes. <PERSON>Miraglia</PERSON>'s earlier <PERSON>Giallo</PERSON>, "The Night Evelyn Came Out of the Grave" (1971) was already a creepy and highly atmospheric film which successfully mixed Giallo with Gothic Horror, but it couldn't possibly compare to this instant personal favorite. "The <ORGANIZATION>Red Queen Kills Seven Times</ORGANIZATION>" is, hands down, one of the most unique and overwhelming Italian Horror films ever made, and no lover of the genre could possibly consider missing it. An incredibly mesmerizing <PERSON>Giallo</PERSON> with strong Gothic elements, "The Red Queen" delivers everything one could hope for in either sub-genre: An inventive and incredibly compelling plot, spine-chilling suspense, a sublimely uncanny setting and a genuinely creepy atmosphere, eerily lush colors, stylish murders, a brilliant score, and, not least, a ravishing female cast lead by the stunningly beautiful <PERSON>Barbara Bouchet</PERSON> - this film simply is one of the most outstanding combinations of elegant beauty and pure terror.<br /><br />The film starts out incredibly in a beautiful Gothic castle in <LOCATION>Germany</LOCATION>. As little girls, <PERSON>Kitty WildenbrÃ</PERSON>¼ck and her sister <PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON> have been fighting when their grandfather tells them the story behind an incredibly uncanny painting: Legend has it that a fiendish Red Lady is to return to the castle every hundred years and kill seven people. Fourteen years later, <PERSON>Kitty</PERSON> (<PERSON>Barbara Bouchet</PERSON>) has become a successful fashion photographer. Suddenly, people begin to get murdered... Director <PERSON>Miraglia</PERSON> had already proved his incredible talent for style, atmosphere and colorful creepiness with "The Night Evelyn Came Out of the Grave" and he makes use of these elements even far more effectively in this gem. "The <ORGANIZATION>Red Queen Kills Seven Times</ORGANIZATION>" is a feast for the eyes indeed, and one of the most overwhelming Italian Horror films both visually and plot-wise. The haunting painting in the Grandfather's castle alone is capable of giving the viewer the goosebumps. The Red Lady (or Red Queen, as she is called in the English title) is arguably the most fiendish figure ever in a Giallo, the spine-chilling laughter that the murders are accompanied by would even be frightening on its own. <br /><br />A sexy female cast is always appreciated, especially in a Giallo, and this one is a prime example for that. The ravishing <PERSON>Barbara Bouchet</PERSON> (one of my favorite actresses) must be one of the most stunningly beautiful ladies ever to appear on screen, and she is a great actress too. <PERSON>Bouchet</PERSON>'s presence has graded up many Italian flicks, among other appearances she starred in three of the greatest Cult-masterpieces of Italian 70s cinema within one year (1972): <PERSON>Fernando Di Leo</PERSON>'s "Milano Calibro 9", <PERSON>Lucio Fulci</PERSON>'s Giallo-highlight "Don't Torture a Duckling" and this unforgettable gem. Apart from the wonderful Miss <PERSON>Bouchet</PERSON>, the film's gorgeous female cast includes sexy young <PERSON>Sybil Danning</PERSON>, <PERSON>Marina Malfatti</PERSON> ("The Night Evelyn Came Out of the Grave"), and other beauties who are not afraid to bare it for the camera. <br /><br />As the whole film, the murders are stylish and extremely elegant, yet frightening and macabre, and some of them are quite gory. <PERSON>Bruno Nicolai</PERSON>'s mesmerizing score is as memorable as it gets, and makes the film's intensely eerie atmosphere even more haunting. The plot is ingeniously convoluted and full of red herrings, the tension-level increses with each passing minute. "The Red Queen..." begins creepy and it stays stunning to the last second. Overall, this is one of the films that I cannot find enough words of praise for. "The <ORGANIZATION>Red Queen Kills Seven Times</ORGANIZATION>" is an absolute masterpiece that easily ranks among the finest <PERSON>Gialli</PERSON> ever made, and a top-priority for every fan of Horror and/or Italian cinema to see. 10/10
60 0 I did not like the idea of the female turtle at all since 1987 we knew the <ORGANIZATION>TMNT</ORGANIZATION> to be four brothers with their teacher Splinter and their enemies and each one of the four brothers are named after the great artists name like <PERSON>Leonardo</PERSON> , <PERSON>Michelangleo</PERSON>, <PERSON>Raphel</PERSON> and <ORGANIZATION>Donatello</ORGANIZATION> so <PERSON>Venus</PERSON> here doesn't have any meaning or playing any important part and I believe that the old TMNT series was much more better than that new one which contains Venus As a female turtle will not add any action to the story we like the story of the TMNT we knew in 1987 to have new enemies in every part is a good point to have some action but to have a female turtle is a very weak point to have some action, we wish to see more new of TMNT series but just as the same characters we knew in 1987 without that female turtle.
61 1 An old family story told to two young girls by their grandfather is brought to life 16 years later as he foretold.<br /><br />People are getting murdered and blood is being spilled and rats are scampering all over and naked bodies are being enjoyed.<br /><br /><PERSON>Kitty</PERSON> (<PERSON>Barbara Bouchet</PERSON>) is the suspect, but we know she is not the killer. Is it <PERSON>Franziska</PERSON> (<PERSON>Marina Malfatti</PERSON>)? Is it <PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON> back from death for revenge? Is it a plot to steal an inheritance? The color is superb in this thriller from <PERSON>Emilio Miraglia</PERSON>, who only did one other Giallo, as far as I know.<br /><br />The only thing that spoiled the film was the appearance that several frames were cut out. Someone calls the police, and suddenly they are there trying to save <PERSON>Kitty</PERSON>.
62 0 This is the biggest insult to TMNT ever. Fortunantely, officially <PERSON>Venus</PERSON> does not exist in canon TMNT. There will never be a female turtle, this took away from the tragic tale of 4 male unique mutants who will never have a family of their own, once gone no more. The biggest mistake was crossing over <ORGANIZATION>Power Rangers</ORGANIZATION> to TMNT with a horrible episode; the turtle's voices were WRONG and they all acted out of character. They could have done such a better job, better designs and animatronics and NO <PERSON>VENUS</PERSON>. <br /><br />don't bother with this people...it's cringe worthy material. the lip flap was slow and unnatural looking. they totally disrespected shredder. the main baddie, some dragonlord dude was corny. the turtles looked corny with things hanging off their bodies, what's with the thing around raph's thigh? the silly looking sculpted plastrons!? <br /><br />If they looked normal, acted in character and got rid of Venus, got rid of the stupid kiddie cartoon sounds...and better writing it could have been good.
63 1 Once upon a time in a castle...... Two little girls are playing in the garden's castle. They are sisters. A blonde little girl (<PERSON>Kitty</PERSON>) and a brunette one (<PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON>). <PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON> steals <PERSON>Kitty</PERSON>'s doll. <PERSON>Kitty</PERSON> pursues <PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON>. Running through long corridors, they reach the room where their grandfather, sitting on an armchair, reads the newspaper. <PERSON>Kitty</PERSON> complains about <PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON>, while <PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON> is looking interestedly at a picture hanging on the wall. <PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON> begins to say repeatedly: "I am the red lady and <PERSON>Kitty</PERSON> is the black lady". Suddenly <PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON> grabs a dagger lying nearby and stabs <PERSON>Kitty</PERSON>'s doll and then cuts her (the doll's) head. A fight ensues. And <PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON> almost uses the dagger against <PERSON>Kitty</PERSON>. The grandfather intervenes and the worst is avoided.<br /><br />Later on, their grandfather tells them the legend related to the picture hanging on the wall in front of them, in which a lady dressed in black is stabbing a lady dressed in red:<br /><br />"A long time ago, a red lady and a black lady lived in the same castle. They were sisters and hated each other. One night, for jealousy reasons, the black lady entered the red lady's room and stabbed her seven times. One year later, the red lady left her grave. She killed six innocent people, and her seventh victim was the black lady. Once every hundred years, the events repeat themselves in this castle and a red lady kills six innocent victims before killing the black lady herself."<br /><br />The grandfather ends his tale by saying that according to the legend, sixteen years from now, the red queen should come again and kill seven times. But he assures them that this is just an old legend.<br /><br />Sixteen years pass.....<br /><br />This is the very beginning of the film. There are many twists and surprises in the film. It's better for you to forget about logic (if you really analyse it, the story doesn't make sense) and just follow the film with its wonderful colors, the gorgeous women, the clothes, the tasteful decor, the lighting effects and the beautiful soundtrack.<br /><br />Enjoy <PERSON>Barbara Bouchet</PERSON>, <PERSON>Sybil Danning</PERSON>, <PERSON>Marina Malfatti</PERSON>, <PERSON>Pia Giancaro</PERSON>, among other goddesses. There's a nude by <PERSON>Sybil Danning</PERSON> lying on a sofa that's something to dream about. And don't forget: The lady in red kills seven times!<br /><br />If you've liked "La <PERSON>Dama Rossa</PERSON>..." check out also "La Notte che Evelyn uscÃ¬ dalla <PERSON>Tomba</PERSON>".
64 0 Sometime in 1998, <PERSON>Saban</PERSON> had acquired the rights to produce a brand-new Ninja Turtles live-action series. Naturally, being a fan of the <ORGANIZATION>TMNT</ORGANIZATION> back in the day, this obviously peaked my interest. So when I started watching the show... to say I was disappointed by the end result is an understatement. Some time later (more like recently), I got a chance to revisit the series.<br /><br />First off, let's talk about some of the positives. They managed to re-create the Turtles' lair as it was last seen in the movies fairly well given the limited budget they threw in with this. There tends to be this darker atmosphere overall in terms of the sets and whatnot. And the Turtle suits, while not the greatest piece of puppetry and whatnot, were functional and seemed pretty sturdy for most of the action stuff that would follow in the series.<br /><br />People tend to complain about getting rid of Shredder quickly and replacing him with these original villains who could have easily been used in a Power Rangers show. But you can only have Shredder get beat so many times before it gets boring and undermines his worth as a villain... and besides, most fans don't realize or don't remember or just plain ignore the fact that in the original comic, the Shredder was offed in the very first issue! Never mind the countless resurrections that would follow. So on a personal standpoint, I was sort of glad they got rid of Shredder because then the anticipation would build to the point where they would eventually bring him back in a later episode. I find that Shredder in small quantities work best because then his encounters with the Turtles are all the more memorable.<br /><br />Unfortunately, they end up replacing him with these original villains who, as stated, seemed more fit for a <ORGANIZATION>Power Rangers</ORGANIZATION> show than a <ORGANIZATION>Ninja Turtles</ORGANIZATION> show. And with these new magic-wielding generics comes a new female magic-wielding turtle, the infamous <PERSON>Venus De Milo</PERSON>. I'll be honest; I never got comfortable with her. I'm not against the idea of a female turtle; I'm just against the idea of one who uses magic and thus sticks out like a sore sight among a clan of ninja turtles who seem somewhat out of their domain. I almost get the impression that this could have easily been the <PERSON>Venus De Milo</PERSON> show dealing with her make-believe enemies and the TMNT are just there to provide the star power (or whatever was left considering the timeframe this was released). Fortunately, they all share the spotlight together.<br /><br />Next Mutation was canned after a season on the air and the creators were more than happy to ignore it. Given time and maybe another season, I really believe this live iteration of the TMNT could have been something and might have gotten a chance at greatness. But while the idea was sound, the execution was flawed (although there are a couple good episodes in this series). As it stands, Next Mutation is one of those oddities in <LOCATION>Turtledom</LOCATION> that is best left buried and forgotten.
65 1 <PERSON>Emilio Miraglia</PERSON>'s first Giallo feature, The Night Evelyn Came Out of the Grave, was a great combination of Giallo and Gothic horror - and this second film is even better! We've got more of the Giallo side of the equation this time around, although <PERSON>Miraglia</PERSON> doesn't lose the Gothic horror stylings that made the earlier film such a delight. <PERSON>Miraglia</PERSON> puts more emphasis on the finer details of the plot this time around, and as a result it's the typical Giallo labyrinth, with characters all over the place and red herrings being thrown in every few minutes. This is a definite bonus for the film, however, as while it can get a little too confusing at times; there's always enough to hold the audience's interest and <PERSON>Miraglia</PERSON>'s storytelling has improved since his earlier movie. The plot opens with a scene that sees two young girls fighting, before their grandfather explains to them the legend behind a rather lurid painting in their castle. The legend revolves around a woman called 'The Red Queen' who, legend has it, returns from the grave every hundred years and kills seven people. A few years later, murders begin to occur...<br /><br />Even though he only made two Giallo's, <PERSON>Miraglia</PERSON> does have his own set of tributes. It's obvious that the colour red is important to him, as it features heavily in both films; and he appears to have something against women called '<PERSON>Evelyn</PERSON>'. He likes castles, Gothic atmospheres and stylish murders too - which is fine by me! <PERSON>Miraglia</PERSON> may be no <PERSON>Argento</PERSON> when it comes to spilling blood, but he certainly knows how to drop an over the top murder into his film; and here we have delights involving a <ORGANIZATION>Volkswagen</ORGANIZATION> Beetle, and a death on an iron fence that is one of my all time favourite Giallo death scenes. The female side of the cast is excellent with the stunning <PERSON>Barbara Bouchet</PERSON> and <PERSON>Marina Malfatti</PERSON> heading up an eye-pleasing cast of ladies that aren't afraid to take their clothes off! The score courtesy of <PERSON>Bruno Nicolai</PERSON> is catchy, and even though it doesn't feature much of the psychedelic rock heard in The Night Evelyn Came Out of the Grave; it fits the film well. The ending is something of a turn-off, as although <PERSON>Miraglia</PERSON> revs up the Gothic atmosphere, it comes across as being more than a little bit rushed and the identity of the murderer is too obvious. But even so, this is a delightfully entertaining <PERSON>Giallo</PERSON> and one that I highly recommend to fans of the genre!
66 0 This is the worst thing the <ORGANIZATION>TMNT</ORGANIZATION> franchise has ever spawned. I was a kid when this came out and I still thought it was deuce, even though I liked the original cartoon.<br /><br />There's this one scene I remember when the mafia ape guy explains to his minions what rhetorical questions are. It's atrocious. Many fans hate on the series for including a female turtle, but that didn't bother me. So much so that I didn't even remember her until I read about the show recently. All in all, it's miserably forgettable.<br /><br />The only okay thing was the theme song. Guilty pleasure, they call it... Nananana ninja...
67 1 This interesting Giallo boosts a typical but still thrilling plot and a really sadistic killer that obviously likes to hunt his victims down before murdering them in gory ways.<br /><br />Directed by <PERSON>Emilio P. Miraglia</PERSON> who, one year earlier, also made the very interesting "La Notte che <PERSON>Evelyn Usci</PERSON> della <PERSON>Tomba</PERSON>" (see also my comment on that one), the film starts off a little slow, but all in all, no time is wasted with unnecessary sub plots or sequences.<br /><br />This film is a German-Italian coproduction, but it was released in <LOCATION>Germany</LOCATION> on video only in a version trimmed by 15 minutes of plot under the stupid title "Horror House". At least the murder scenes, which will satisfy every gorehound, are fully intact, and the viewer still gets the killer's motive at the end. But the Italian version containing all the footage is still the one to look for, of course.<br /><br />A convincing <PERSON>Giallo</PERSON> with obligatory twists and red herrings, "La Dama Rossa Uccide Sette Volte" is highly recommended to Giallo fans and slightly superior to <PERSON>Miraglia</PERSON>'s above mentioned other thriller.
68 0 Not only is it a disgustingly made low-budget bad-acted movie, but the plot itself is just STUPID!!!<br /><br />A mystic man that eats women? (And by the looks, not virgin ones)<br /><br />Ridiculous!!! If youÂ´ve got nothing better to do (like sleeping) you should watch this. Yeah right.
69 1 What a fun movie! If you're a Giallo fan, Red Queen Kills 7 <ORGANIZATION>Times</ORGANIZATION> is a real winner. To begin with, it's hard to go wrong with <PERSON>Barbara Bouchet</PERSON> and <PERSON>Marina Malfatti</PERSON> in the same Giallo. Both are wonderful - especially the wide-eyed innocent <PERSON>Bouchet</PERSON> as the guilt ridden woman fearing for her life. The kill scenes in Red Queen Kills 7 <ORGANIZATION>Times</ORGANIZATION> are especially nice and feature enough blood to make most fans happy. One of the first murders comes rather unexpectedly and really gets the movie off to a good start. The killer, The Red Queen, is one of the most over-the-top and interesting looking murderers I've seen in an Italian movie. The 70s sets and fashions are wonderful. In fact, all the visuals are interesting with the laughing Red Queen running across the bridge at night being one of my favorite moments in the film. The convoluted plot held my interest throughout. Finally, <PERSON>Bruno Nicolai</PERSON>'s score may be the best I've heard from the composer. The main theme is so memorable I haven't been able to get it out of my head for two days.<br /><br />The only two issues I have with Red Queen Kills 7 Times come in the film's finale. First, the person responsible for the murders is far too easy to spot. If you've seen more than a couple Gialli, you won't have any problem determining who is behind the killings. Second, the ending feels a little too rushed and, as a result, is a bit confusing. I'm definitely not one who needs every plot point spelled out to me, but I'll admit to being at a loss to explain it all. A second viewing might just clear this up.
70 0 <ORGANIZATION>Sexo Cannibal</ORGANIZATION>, or <PERSON>Devil Hunter</PERSON> as it's more commonly known amongst English speaking audiences, starts with actress & model <PERSON>Laura Crawford</PERSON> (<PERSON>Ursula Buchfellner</PERSON> as <PERSON>Ursula Fellner</PERSON>) checking out locations for her new film along with her assistant <PERSON>Jane</PERSON> (<PERSON>Gisela Hahn</PERSON>). After a long days work <PERSON>Laura</PERSON> is relaxing in the bath of her room when two very dubious character's named <PERSON>Chris</PERSON> (<PERSON>Werner Pochath</PERSON>) & <PERSON>Thomas</PERSON> (Antonio Mayans) burst in & kidnap her having been helped by the treacherous <PERSON>Jane</PERSON>. <PERSON>Laura</PERSON>'s agent gets on the blower to rent-a-hero <PERSON>Peter Weston</PERSON> (<PERSON>Al Cliver</PERSON>) who is informed of the situation, the kidnappers have <PERSON>Laura</PERSON> on an isolated island & are demanding a 6 million ransom. <PERSON>Peter</PERSON> is told that he will be paid 200,000 to get her back safely & a further 10% of the 6 million if he brings that back as well, faster than a rat up a drain pipe <PERSON>Peter</PERSON> & his <LOCATION>Vietnam</LOCATION> Vet buddy helicopter pilot <PERSON>Jack</PERSON> are on the island & deciding on how to save <PERSON>Laura</PERSON>. So, the kidnappers have <ORGANIZATION>Laura & Peter</ORGANIZATION> has the 6 million but neither want to hand them over that much. Just to complicate things further this particular isolated island is home to a primitive tribe (hell, in all the generations they've lived there they've only managed to build one straw hut, now that's primitive) who worship some cannibal monster dude (<PERSON>Burt Altman</PERSON>) with bulging eyes as a God with human sacrifices & this cannibal has a liking for young, white female flesh & intestines...<br /><br />This Spanish, French & German co-production was co-written & directed by the prolific <PERSON>Jesus Franco</PERSON> who also gets the credit for the music as well. Sexo Cannibal has gained a certain amount of notoriety here in the <LOCATION>UK</LOCATION> as it was placed on the 'Video Nasties' list in the early 80's under it's alternate Devil Hunter title & therefore officially classed as obscene & banned, having said that I have no idea why as it is one bad film & even <PERSON>Franco</PERSON>, who isn't afraid to be associated with a turkey, decides he wants to hide under the pseudonym of <PERSON>Clifford Brown</PERSON>. I'd imagine even the most die-hard <PERSON>Franco</PERSON> fan would have a hard time defending this thing. The script by <PERSON>Franco</PERSON>, erm sorry I mean <PERSON>Clifford Brown</PERSON> & <PERSON>Julian Esteban</PERSON> as <PERSON>Julius Valery</PERSON> who was obviously another one less than impressed with the finished product & wanted his named removed, is awful. It's as simple & straight forward as that. For a start the film is so boring it's untrue, the kidnap plot is one of the dullest I've ever seen without the slightest bit of tension or excitement involved & the horror side of things don't improve as we get a big black guy with stupid looking over-sized bloodshot eyes plus two tame cannibal scenes. As a horror film Sexo Cannibal fails & as an action adventure it has no more success, this is one to avoid.<br /><br />Director <PERSON>Franco</PERSON> shows his usual incompetence throughout, a decapitated head is achieved by an actor lying on the ground with large leaves placed around the bottom of his neck to try & give the impression it's not attached to anything! The cannibal scenes are poor, the action is lame & it has endless scenes of people randomly walking around the jungle getting from 'A' to 'B' & not really doing anything when they get there either. It becomes incredibly dull & tedious to watch after about 10 minutes & don't forget this thing goes on for 94 minutes in it's uncut state. I also must mention the hilarious scene when <PERSON>Al Cliver</PERSON> is supposed to be climbing a cliff, this is achieved by <PERSON>Franco</PERSON> turning his camera on it's side & having <PERSON>Cliver</PERSON> crawl along the floor! Just look at the way his coat hangs & the way he never grabs onto to anything as he just pulls himself along! The gore isn't that great & as far as Euro cannibal films go this is very tame, there are some gross close ups of the cannibals mouth as it chews bits of meat, a man is impaled on spikes, there's some blood & a handful of intestines. There's a fair bit of nudity in Sexo Cannibal & an unpleasant rape scene.<br /><br /><ORGANIZATION>Sexo Cannibal</ORGANIZATION> must have had a low budget & I mean low. This is a shoddy poorly made film with awful special effects & rock bottom production values. The only decent thing about it is the jungle setting which at least looks authentic. The music sucks & sound effects become annoying as there is lots of heavy breathing whenever the cannibal is on screen. The acting sucks, the whole thing was obviously dubbed anyway but no one in this thing can act.<br /><br /><ORGANIZATION>Sexo Cannibal</ORGANIZATION> is a terrible film that commits the fatal mistake of being as boring as hell. The only good things I can say is that it has a certain sleazy atmosphere to it & those close ups of the cannibal chewing meat are pretty gross. Anyone looking for a decent cinematic experience should give <ORGANIZATION>Sexo Cannibal</ORGANIZATION> as wide a berth as possible, one to avoid.
71 1 When I saw the elaborate DVD box for this and the dreadful Red Queen figurine, I felt certain I was in for a big disappointment, but surprise, surprise, I loved it. Convoluted nonsense of course and unforgivable that such a complicated denouement should be rushed to the point of barely being able to read the subtitles, let alone take in the ridiculous explanation. These quibbles apart, however, the film is a dream. Fabulous ladies in fabulous outfits in wonderful settings and the whole thing constantly on the move and accompanied by a wonderful <PERSON>Bruno Nicolai</PERSON> score. He may not be <PERSON>Morricone</PERSON> but in these lighter pieces he might as well be so. Really enjoyable with lots of colour, plenty of sexiness, some gory kills and minimal police interference. Super.
72 0 This film seemed way too long even at only 75 minutes. The problem with jungle horror films is that there is always way too much footage of people walking (through the jungle, up a rocky cliff, near a river or lake) to pad out the running time. The film is worth seeing for the laughable and naked native zombie with big bulging, bloody eyes which is always accompanied on the soundtrack with heavy breathing and lots of reverb. Eurotrash fans will be plenty entertained by the bad English dubbing, gratuitous female flesh and very silly makeup jobs on the monster and native extras. For a zombie/cannibal flick this was pretty light on the gore but then I probably didn't see an uncut version.
73 1 Another good Stooge short!Christine <PERSON>McIntyre</PERSON> is so lovely and evil and the same time in this one!She is such a great actress!The Stooges are very good and especially <PERSON>Shemp</PERSON> and Larry!This to is a good one to watch around Autumn time!
74 0 <ORGANIZATION>Devil Hunter</ORGANIZATION> gained notoriety for the fact that it's on the <ORGANIZATION>DPP</ORGANIZATION> 'Video Nasty' list, but it really needn't have been. Many films on the list where there for God (and <ORGANIZATION>DPP</ORGANIZATION>) only known reasons, and while this isn't the tamest of the bunch; there isn't a lot here that warrants banning...which is a shame because I never would have sat through it where it not for the fact that it's on 'the shopping list'. The plot actually gives the film a decent base - or at least more of a decent base than most cannibal films - and it follows an actress who is kidnapped and dragged off into the <LOCATION>Amazon</LOCATION> jungle. A hunter is then hired to find her, but along the way he has to brave the natives, lead by a man who calls himself "The Devil" (hence the title). The film basically just plods along for eighty five minutes and there really aren't many scenes of interest. It's a real shame that <PERSON>Jess Franco</PERSON> ended up making films like this because the man clearly has talent; as seen by films such as The Diabolical Dr Z, <PERSON>Venus</PERSON> in Furs, Faceless and She Kills in Ecstasy, but unfortunately his good films are just gems amongst heaps of crap and <PERSON>Devil Hunter</PERSON> is very much a part of the crap. I saw this film purely because I want to be able to say I've seen everything on the <ORGANIZATION>DPP</ORGANIZATION>'s list (just two more to go!), and I'm guessing that's why most other people who have seen it, saw it. But if you're not on the lookout for Nasties; there really is no reason to bother with this one.
75 1 Of the elements that make this the best at this point, I have to say #1 is <PERSON>Christine McIntire</PERSON>. <PERSON>Shemp</PERSON>'s scene when poisoned and her reaction are truly magnificent. I imagine that, as one poster suggested, <PERSON>Christine</PERSON> was trying to hold back laughter during that scene, but it actually made her seem even more deliciously evil, to be smiling at <ORGANIZATION>Shemp</ORGANIZATION>'s possibly dying.<br /><br />Another character who helps this stand out is the Goon. His look was a great cross between horrific and comedic goof-ball. Hardly a character I would choose to meet in a dark alley or, for that matter anywhere. I would have preferred a bit of true whodunit mystery in this, but hey, when a short is this good, who's going to complain. Not I.
